Rabbit!
I didn't say it was okay to look!
I was thinking of showing it to Mom, too...
Rabbit?
It isn't just any ol' rabbit!
It's awesome!
It's missing now... but it's out there somewhere.
Once we find it, we can go anywhere we want.
Done!                  Done!
Matching!
You're amazing!
You complete my fate
The world unwinds inside of me
The halo crawls away
You refill my place
Come and save me
Believe in me and drink the wine and take my hand and fill me up
Golo presents
Come and save me
meditation    summoning
We may have to clear out of here.
Over here, over here.
Mom.
Timothy.
Where've you been?
C'mon.
Let's go.
There've been more surveillance units.
That's right,
after someone came here...
What are you gonna do?
Why don't you go somewhere else?
Why'd you come here in the first place?
That's...
Of course it's because he's the Chosen One.
This man is a famous revolutionary in Romdeau.
He took the dome's system head-on
and directed the resistance's activities.
He is a warrior.
H-Hey, Mr. Hoody,
wait a minute-
You saw his brilliant marksmanship, didn't you?
Even if a whole army of surveillance units were to come,
it'd be child's play to him.
Wow...
Romdeau is near collapse;
citizens are all turning into
refugees and heading for the Commune.
Who would have thought that the city's last
resort would be to launch a series of attacks on us.
Officials are struggling to prevent the increase in deviants, but...
Sadly, they don't realize that
it only enflames Vincent, the revolutionary warrior's, will to fight.
What fools.
Mr. Hoody...
"Revolutionary warrior"?
As if I give a rat's ass about what's happening in Romdeau.
I don't want to get dragged into this mess.
What are you saying?
This is a revolution in which our
freedom and dignity are at stake-
If we get killed,
freedom doesn't mean shit.
She's right.
If we get killed-
There won't be any more victims.
How can you be so sure?
Because...
Ah, yes.
It's because a certain source
has informed me of where the surveillance units will attack.
I kept this a secret from everyone to prevent confusion,
but I'm currently in negotiations with Romdeau
authorities regarding the Commune's autonomy.
The enemy is desperate.
They even begged us to return to Romdeau.
Seriously?
Sounds like a dream.
You barely escaped with your life.
If I hadn't saved you,
you would've been beaten.
But...
I don't know about lying to them...
You escaped unscathed because I thought quickly on my feet,
but it was a close call.
Extremely close.
We can just let Hoody handle this.
What, Quinn?
Are you gonna pick another fight?
Not really.
I'm just wondering how Hoody's making contact with Romdeau,
that's all.
Ah, this is the Commune.
Calling Romdeau.
Over.
What's the matter?
Quinn said...
What?
All right.
Seems they don't care about appearances anymore.
They're insisting that I change sides.
They're desperate, I tell you.
Someone from Romdeau is coming here?
Who?
A negotiator?
A negotiator would be-
Maybe...
they're coming to welcome us?
W-Well...
I suppose that's a possibility.
We can go back to Romdeau!
Lucky us!
All right!
Hey, is that what they call a radio?
Worrying was a waste of time.
See, I told you.
We even have a revolutionary warrior.
We're invincible.
Uh...
Where's that warrior, anyway?
Found you!
You're playing hide-and-seek, right?
Me too!
Go away!
Roger!
Hide-and-seek, hide-and-seek!
Don't think he'd be here.
Yeah.
Done!
Me too!
Don't be a copycat!
What do you think you can accomplish
with that gloomy face, revolutionary warrior?
Sorry...
Actually, this is all your-
Are you just like them?
Hanging on to me, yet independent enough to complain?
I'm the only one who thinks about the Commune's welfare.
Don't worry.
As long as we get through this, there will be peace.
Worst case,
Note: Centzon Totochtin, from Aztec mythology, are the four hundred divine
rabbits of the Aztec pantheon who preside over parties and drunkenness.
we'll escape with the Centzon Totochtin.
"Centzon"...?
Four hundred rabbits.
Rabbits?
Found a rabbit!
Oh, hey-
Hop!
Wait.
Well, only Hoody's seen it.
I have no idea what kind of vehicle it is.
"Four hundred rabbits"...
What a joke of a name.
Who knows where he hid it.
Why did he hide it?
He said something about the outside being dangerous,
but he just wants to keep everyone here.
He wants to take us down with him.
I'm scared
that lies will lead to more lies
and one day, something terrible will happen.
People are pitiful, aren't they?
Every single one of them.
When was the negotiator coming again?
Soon.
From where?
Probably...
from over there.
I think he might pretend to come from over there,
then come swooshing in from over that way.
Hoody, he's here!
He's here!
Who?
This way, please.
The negotiator.
I can't hear them at all.
What are they talking about?
Can't see the negotiator's face, either.
Think Hoody can cut us a good deal?
You don't seem to be the same negotiator as before.
Would you tell us your name at least?
This is going nowhere.
What did you come here for?
Did you get too scared to continue negotiations?
Are you going to use force?
He'll take you on then.
U-Um...
It's me,
Vincent.
Re-l...
Mayer.
I've come to take you back.
What?
What is this about?
You're coming back to Romdeau.
As if I could do that...
on such short notice...
What's going on?
Once you deviate from Romdeau, you can never go back.
Why?
Why this man?
Be quiet!
Go over there!
Okay!
Vincent, we're going back.
Wait!
I won't let you take Vincent!
Do you want to get yourself killed?
Re-l, it's me.
Can you hear me?
Chief,
we have a report from the Security Bureau-
Re-l.
What?
Get out of the way.
What's going on?
There are humans all over the place outside.
Re-l...
I told you not to get in touch with outsiders...
They're right here in front of me.
I can't pretend they don't exist.
Why did you keep them a secret from me?
I...
didn't want to cause you unnecessary concern.
It's not just about PROXY anymore.
PROXY?
That's a dangerous topic.
Get away from him!
Dammit!
How...
do you know of that monster?
The PROXY, a monster?
You're a naïve young lady.
He's laughing.
He totally has the upper hand.
They're called monsters and
demons and such, but that's all hogwash.
PROXIES are magicians.
They can shapeshift into anything.
They can easily make themselves vanish.
They can sneak into the human mind and manipulate it at will.
They could produce lightning and incinerate this area in an instant.
They've called forth planets that spout flames too.
Will you be quiet?!
Get out!
Stay out until I say you can come back in!
Tag, tag!
Just between you and me,
there is more than one PROXY.
Once you set one foot outside, they're everywhere.
Just counting the ones I've seen with my own eyes...
Five?
Well...
This is a waste of time.
Let's go, Vincent.
Wait!
If you insist, I have no choice.
I can make a special exception
and tell you where PROXY is.
However, only if you'll accept our conditions.
Re-l, it's me.
Can you hear me?
What is it?
First,
accept our autonomy
The situation has changed.
and cease all hostilities immediately.
Come back ASAP.
I intend to do that anyway.
You're surprisingly obliging.
Second, establish friendly relations with us immediately,
Were you able to bring Vincent Law into your custody?
Of course.
and let those who wish to return to Romdeau-
Quiet!
Go over there!
But the surveillance units show up over there-
There are no surveillance units during negotiation!
All right.
We have to hurry, Vincent.
We don't have any more time.
The Security Bureau's preparing
a sweep operation of the Commune.
If you stay here, you'll be killed too.
Sweep operation?
What do you mean?
You just agreed to establish friendly relations with us-
Come with me, Vincent.
Are soldiers coming here?
Are they going to mess things up?
What will happen to me?
What should I do?
Let go of me!
You...
Are you going to abandon us?
Are you going to run away even though we helped you?
Hey,
I said, don't be a copycat.
You should draw what you like, Pino.
What do I like to draw?
Don't ask me.
Just draw stuff that comes to mind,
like food you really want to eat now.
I don't eat food.
Oh, right.
Then try closing your eyes.
Remember stuff that was fun.
If you remember something,
all you have to do is draw that.
Guess we're gonna go back.
We have to pack.
Huh?
Surveillance units.
I thought they weren't gonna come anymore.
Maybe they came to get us.
We're going, Vincent.
U-Um...
Couldn't we take the others with us?
Um, I just can't go back by myself.
Well...
Once you're back in Romdeau,
you'll forget about them soon enough-
about the Commune and everything else.
You'll just go back to the life you had before.
Would everything
really go back the way it was?
Don't worry.
I'll prove your innocence.
That's not it!
I mean...
I've found out
that there is a world outside.
Even if I go back to Romdeau now...
I can't become a model citizen.
Romdeau is the only place to return to.
Where else will you go?
This trash heap?
Don't make me laugh.
You're right.
I wonder where I should go.
Neither here nor Romdeau are right.
I might as well go back to where I was born...
To that fallen dome?
Are you insane?
Watch out!
Stop it!
She's amazing.
She can do anything.
Timothy?
Re-l?
Daedalus...
The transmission got taken out.
I can't move like this.
Re-l...
Don't!
If you are exposed to the outside air, you'll-
Re-l!
Don't go!
What are you?
I need to make contact with Romdeau ASAP.
Is that a radio?
W-Well...
No, play a higher sound there.
What is this?!
I don't understand.
What's going on?!
Like this.
Get the radio out here.
Quinn, come with me.
What's the matter?
Hurry, hurry!
I have to contact Romdeau now.
Calm down.
Drink this.
Shut up!
What's going on?
Why is PROXY here?
Why?
Why does it only show up where you are?
Answer me!
What in the world...
are you?
Miss Re-l!
Like I said,
Timothy won't give the book back to me.
Right, right.
He won't even answer me.
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
Please
could
you
stop
the
noise,
I'm
trying
to
get
some
rest
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
From
all
the
un
born
chic
head
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
What's
that...?
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
I
may
be
para
noid,
but
not
an
droid
It prevents us from going back.
The doors leading back will open
when the balance between the powers that attack us collapses.
meditation  homecoming